Guide to the Laurence MacDaniels papers, [ca. 1915]-1986.
Laurence MacDaniels papers,
- United Nations Relief and Rehabilitation Administration 1945 Naples Cairo Albania Mission Rotary Talk, Kiwanis, Etc., 1945 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  lecture notes and correspondence
- 1971 Alumni Reunion Tour Guide Cornell Plantations, 1971 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  correspondence with R. M. Lewis and information regarding Plantations tours
- Miscellaneous 1975, 1977-78, 1975-1978 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  Waltox notes, correspondence with R. Jaynes, miscellaneous conservation literature, Plantations material, fluoridation
- General Correspondence 1973, 1973 (Box 22, Folder 6)
- Eames Memorial 1973, 1973 (Box 22, Folder 7)
- Department Memos 1973, 1973 (Box 22, Folder 8)
- Dormancy, Date Unknown (Box 22, Folder 9)
  copy of "Dormancy in Seeds of Woody Plants"
- Cornell Correspondence 1971, 1971 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  letter from R. N. Klippstein
- Compost 1973, 1973 (Box 22, Folder 11)
  correspondence and copies of Extension Bulletin
- Weather Records 1973, 1973 (Box 22, Folder 12)
- Plantations 1971-2, 1971-1972 (Box 22, Folder 13)
  meeting minutes, director's report
- Organic Gardening Compost 1971, 1971 (Box 22, Folder 14)
- Natural Areas 1971 and 1973, 1971-1973 (Box 22, Folder 15)
- Nuts Miscellaneous Stencil, Date Unknown (Box 22, Folder 16)
  miscellaneous nut literature
- Nut Growing Letters 1973-74, 1973-1974 (Box 22, Folder 17)
- Nut Extension Letters 1973, 1973 (Box 22, Folder 18)
- 1973-74 Miscellaneous, 1973-1974 (Box 22, Folder 19)
  monthly meteorological reports, miscellaneous correspondence including J. G. Seeley, et a1 various newspaper clippings
- 1971-2 Miscellaneous 1968, 1968-1972 (Box 22, Folder 20)
  Nota Bene: includes letter from L. H. Bailey to LHM regarding article on hot house growing of grapes, various newspaper clippings, miscellaneous correspondence, etc.
- [envelope] Men's Garden Club Cayuga Meeting 1972-73, 1972-1973 (Box 22, Folder 21)
  Men's Garden Club material
- Cornell Plantations 1970-71, 1970-1971 (Box 22, Folder 22)
  miscellany
- Cornell Plantations 1970-71, 1970-1971 (Box 22, Folder 23)
- Plantations - Arboretum Planting Plans Committee Reports 1971, 1971 (Box 22, Folder 24)
- Miscellaneous Plantations Material Not in Folder, Date Unknown (Box 22, Folder 25)
- Writing Lilies Current, Date Unknown (Box 22, Folder 26)
  notes and 1st draft manuscript
- Horticulture in Southeast Asia Bulletin - Windsor, Date Unknown (Box 22, Folder 27)
  copy: Thoughts on the Future of Horticulture in Indonesia
- Ithaca Property 1960, 1960 (Box 22, Folder 28)
  literature sent from City Planning Board
- [envelope] Old Passport - Older Material - Philippine Project, Date Unknown (Box 22, Folder 29)
- Senior Citizens Council Organization 1955, 1955 (Box 22, Folder 30)
  general material
- Miscellaneous 1962, 1978, 1962-1978 (Box 22, Folder 31)
- Recovery of Logged Glen - Saturday Night Talk 1969, 1969 (Box 22, Folder 32)
  correspondence with Audrey O'Connor
- Men's Garden Club 1973 Directors, 1973 (Box 22, Folder 33)
  miscellaneous material from Men's Garden Club
- Lightly's Lily Paper - 1966, 1966 (Box 22, Folder 34)
  correspondence regarding paper and 1st draft of manuscripts with editorial notes
- Men's Garden Club Working Folder, Date Unknown (Box 22, Folder 35)
- Miscellaneous 1979, 1979 (Box 22, Folder 36)
  forestry talk in Syracuse
- Cornell Plantations May June July 1971 Natural Areas Problems Orchid Bog, 1971 (Box 22, Folder 37)
  miscellaneous related material and notes
- American Fisheries Society File 7, Date Unknown (Box 22, Folder 38)
  miscellaneous correspondence and literature from American Fisheries Society, no dates
- Loose Material Cornell Plantations 1974, 1974 (Box 22, Folder 39)
- Growing Degree Days Data 1972, 1972 (Box 22, Folder 40)
  weather observations
- No Title, Date Unknown (Box 22, Folder 41)
  contains 1 photograph with Helen Cochran (Mrs. Mac's mother (?), vaccination verification, note from Military Liaison, Albania - 2 10 lire notes, one issued before war and one "Allied Military Currency"
- 1971 (Box 22, Folder 42)
  copy of outline and draft of manuscript "Trees in Trouble"
- [envelope] G. L. Slate Obit Memorial Statement, Date Unknown (Box 22, Folder 43)
  Necrology
- Miscellaneous 1975, 1975 (Box 22, Folder 44)
- Plantations 1972, 1972 (Box 22, Folder 45)
  miscellaneous Plantations material
- Plantations Ad Hoc Committee August 1969 Dave Dunlop, Harlow Banks, Dick Lewis, Audrey O'Connor, John Seeley, Ex Of Toomajian, 1969-08 (Box 22, Folder 46)
  notes, meeting minutes, etc.
- Attention - September 1963, 1963-09 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  various correspondence August-September 1963
- Attention - General 1966, 1966 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  various correspondence including fluoridation correspondence with Lo Pinto, envelope of color negatives
- Unfinished Need Attention 1959-60, 1959-1960 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  various personal correspondence, correspondence regarding Yugoslavia, judging schedules for nuts - Michigan State, Cornell University, Pedro Rodrigo in Philippines, lily society trophies list 1960, Men's Garden Club - Indonesia, postcards - birthday greetings
- Answered Not Filed 1962-3, 1962-1963 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  personal correspondence with Ibon in Philippines; Mann Library; American Horticultural Society; Yugoslavia; Tompkins County Health Department regarding fluoride; D. Watson, Michigan State University; Oberlin College; George Weber, Pennsylvania Nut Growers; Gilbert Becker, Climax Michigan 1 Christmas greetings; Senator Otto Passman - regarding fluoride; Paul Fanning, United States Agency for International Development; Hawaiian Botanical Society newsletter; USDA Forest Experiment Station Jesse Diller; recommendation for John McDanial; Gilbert Smith Nurseries; Gustav Swanson, NUSCA- Department Conservation; Lewis Durland, Cornell University Treasurer; Jesse Diller - regarding chest
- 1961 Current File To Be Answered, 1961 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  W. H. Stimning - Wholesale Growers regarding lilies; Clark Bond of Washington nut trees; returned letter to Mr. J. K. Ball, Arkansas; Halsey Knapp of Rotary International personal; Putnam Payne of United Fruit regarding Paul Allen and germ plasm; Rich Hulbert of Cleary, Gottlieb; Steen and Hamilton regarding arboretum case and trip to Jugoslavia; personal from Rey of Philadelphia; Jean le Roy - Museum of Natural History - Paris regarding morphology of Jugoslavs; D. L. Umali of Jugoslavia regarding Baker Memorial Scholarship; Jean Berke Travel Service - New York City regarding touring; J. Russel Smith - walnuts; erosion and Jugoslavia; personal Valesco Philadelphia; personal, Pelongco from College of Agriculture Philippines; Dr. Reid Brooks of Agriculture Experiment Station Davis, CA re walnuts; Pancho of Philippines - personal and agricultural request; Ramon, Athens, GA personal; F. P. McWhorter, plant pathology - USDA regarding congratulations for Philippines lily; Leslie Woodruff Fairyland Lily Garden confirm lily order; lists of crops and times of shipment from American Arabian Oil Company, Saudi Arabia, personal from Ibon; personal from Julia N. Clark to Mrs. King; from Dr. and Mrs. Benedict V. Farata - regarding joining North American Lily Society and information on raising lilies; from Monty Moves of USA operations Mission to Yugoslavia - regarding $100 payment on VolksWagon; personal from Satins
- Answered Not Filed 1961, 1961 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  personal Ilion, Philippines; Roy E. Marshall, secretary treasurer Ame
- Attention Not Answered 1962, 1962 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  Envelope of slides, prints and negatives of palms in Phil
- L. H. MacDaniels 1962 Answered Not Filed, 1962 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  correspondence with Seeley, et al; law firm in Boston regarding Arnold Arboretum Case; personal correspondence with Ibon of Philippines; letter from G. S. Butts - regarding AGR Building fund
- Personal and Official Unanswered Older Material, 1961-1962 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  includes G. L. Slate (and F. Abbey) and LHM while in Jugoslavia (1961); correspondence with various individuals in USDA as well as Cornell University professors from Yugoslavia (1961-2; Keyes Metcalf, A. J. Eames; A. W. Dinmck, AMS Pridham, J. G. Seeley
- African Trip 1966-67, 1966-1967 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  includes itineraries, Correspondence regarding trip to Africa and Turkey, notes for talk to Saturday night about African trip (5/27/67); maps, brochures, pamphlets - regarding trip and East Africa
- Envelope - Africa, Date Unknown (Box 24, Folder 5)
  pamphlets, brochures, etc.
- Arnold Arboretum, 1957-1962 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  correspondence and general material 1957-62
- American Horticultural Society 1961, 1961 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  correspondence, newsletters, certificate of membership
- American Association for the Advancement of Science, 1943-11-23 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  certificate of life membership Nov. 23, 1943
- American Society for Horticultural Science, 1965 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  various newsletters, certificate of fellowship 17 August 1965
- Berke Tour 1966, 1966 (Box 24, Folder 10)
  LHM leader, garden tour - maps, brochures, etc.
- Envelope - Anti-Fluoridation Campaign, Date Unknown (Box 24, Folder 11)
  receipts, etc.
- Berke Travel Service 1965-66, 1965-1966 (Box 24, Folder 12)
  correspondence, newsletters, brochures
- Bergen Swamp - Permanent File, Date Unknown (Box 24, Folder 13)
  newsletters, brochures, pamphlets
- Envelope - Nursery Catalogues - 1962 Lilies Only, 1962 (Box 24, Folder 14)
- Cayuga Lake Basin Water Resources Planning Board Conservation - Watershed 1965, 1965 (Box 24, Folder 15)
  notes, newspaper clippings, newsletters, minutes of meetings, correspondence
- New York State Conservation Council 1965, 1965 (Box 24, Folder 16)
  correspondence and newsletters
- Fluoridation 1967, 1967 (Box 24, Folder 17)
  booklets, newspaper articles, correspondence, National Health Federation material, etc.
- Fluoridation 1966, 1966 (Box 24, Folder 18)
- Fluoridation 1972, 1972 (Box 24, Folder 19)
- Fluoridation - January 1966 Not Filed, 1966-01 (Box 24, Folder 20)
- L. H. MacDaniels - United Fund as Related to Fluoridation 1965, 1965 (Box 24, Folder 21)
- Fishing - Resorts and General, Date Unknown (Box 24, Folder 22)
  pamphlets, brochures etc.
- (Blue Folder From American Dental Association) Fluoridation, Date Unknown (Box 24, Folder 23)
  the "other side"
- Envelope - Isaak Walton League of America, 1965 (Box 24, Folder 24)
  Contributions and Expenditures for Campaign - 1965
- Lily Catalogues, Date Unknown (Box 24, Folder 25)
- Envelope - Lloyd Library 1965, 1965 (Box 24, Folder 26)
  correspondence with G. H. M. Lawrence
- A. D. Little Company Nigeria 1963, 1963 (Box 24, Folder 27)
  correspondence regarding development of integrated pineapple and citrus industry in West Nigeria
- U.S. Congress Matt McHugh, 1977 (Box 24, Folder 28)
  correspondence - 1977
- MacDaniels Letters from Yugoslavia and Patzcuaro, 1950-1962 (Box 24, Folder 29)
  includes correspondence between LHM and Department of Public Works (1950-52); personal family letters from Yugoslavia (1961-2); some personal family from west coast
- Envelope Near East Foundation, 1943-1946 (Box 24, Folder 30)
  pamphlet on Near East Foundation and American University of Beirut (1946); correspondence with various individuals at Near East Foundation (1946); employment agreement between LHM and Near East Foundation (1943)
- Northern Nut Growers Association Nutshell 1961-67, 1961-1967 (Box 24, Folder 31)
  various copies of newsletter
- Copy Oberlin College Class 1912 45th Reunion June 1957, 1957-06 (Box 24, Folder 32)
- L. H. MacDaniels - Personal - Permanent, 1963-1973 (Box 24, Folder 33)
  includes biographies, notes or "personal statements" on life, health, etc.; letter to daughters - 1963-73
- Personal May - 1974, 1974 (Box 24, Folder 34)
  includes correspondence from G. L. Slate (1974); copy of "Save the Finger Lakes Glens"; various letters - regarding bunch disease of walnuts, Northern Nut Growers Association business, North American Lily Society business; conservation efforts; etc.
- Writing - Manuscripts - Philosophy (envelope), 1970 (Box 24, Folder 35)
  includes various "philosophical" statements (not LHM) and correspondence with LHM - 1970
- Philosophical Statement - Article - 2nd draft, 1974-1977 (Box 24, Folder 36)
  copies of "The Implications of Science in a Philosophy of Life" and correspondence (1974-1977)
- Population Explosion, 1967 (Box 24, Folder 37)
  article by Planned Parenthood 1967
- Copy of "Oberlin Today" 1962, 1962 (Box 24, Folder 38)
  includes excerpts from LHM's 50th reunion alumni address with photo of LHM on cover
- Plantations 1965, 1964-1965 (Box 24, Folder 39)
  copies of Plantations bulletin 1964
- Cornell Plantations, 1965-1966 (Box 24, Folder 40)
  sponsors lists 1965-6
- Copy - Cornell Countryman November 1962, 1962-11 (Box 24, Folder 41)
  article about LHM in Yugoslavia with walnuts
- Dr. Baty - Patzcuaro Project 1962-3, 1962-1963 (Box 24, Folder 42)
  5 copies of "Fruit Growing in Patzcuaro Area,'' correspondence with Dr. H. F. Baty; Dr. Facci, assorted photos; supply lists; information sheets about Crefal-Montana Project; draft of "Observations on the Temperature Limitation of the Apple in Tropical America" by Damon Boynton
- Patzcuaro - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1963 (Box 24, Folder 43)
  list draft of fruit report; notes; "The Zurumutaro Experiment" by H. F. Baty 1963
- Personal - Philippines - Yugoslavia 1964-1970, 1964-1970 (Box 24, Folder 44)
- Resort and Fishing - Folders and Places To Go, Date Unknown (Box 24, Folder 45)
  travel brochures
- Cornell University - Research Club, Date Unknown (Box 24, Folder 46)
  membership lists and memorabilia
- Rhododendrons, Date Unknown (Box 24, Folder 47)
  extension bulletins
- West Hill Park 1964-66, 1964-1966 (Box 24, Folder 48)
  includes maps (survey map for billing 1922); correspondence with City of Ithaca; newspaper clippings; photos
- Writing - Miscellaneous Old Manuscripts, Date Unknown (Box 24, Folder 49)
  various manuscripts and related correspondence including A. J. Eames; W. H. Chandler; Editor of Ithaca Journal
- Saturday Nite and Rotary Talks - Manuscripts and Notes Including "Perhaps It Is Later Than You Think", Date Unknown (Box 24, Folder 50)
- Correspondence and receipts, Date Unknown (Box 25)
  horticulture related
- Oberlin College, 1977-1978 (Box 25)
  includes correspondence 1977-1978 printed material
- George Slate material, Date Unknown (Box 25)
- Tree crops, Date Unknown (Box 25)
  notes and correspondence; nut manuscripts; Waltox notes; various correspondence and newspaper articles
- Cayuga Lake Conservation Association 1974-, 1974 (Box 26)
- Florida 1973, 1973 (Box 26)
  Materials to Take February 1973
- Florida - letters, Date Unknown (Box 26)
- Correspondence from Mexico with photo of school building under construction, Date Unknown (Box 26)
- Correspondence from H. D. Hughes, Date Unknown (Box 26)
- Cornell Oral History, Date Unknown (Box 26)
  Coleman Interviews includes correspondence and transcripts
- Environmental Management Council 1974 May, 1974 (Box 26)
  includes letter to editor, Ithaca Journal
- Correspondence, Date Unknown (Box 26)
- Northern Nut Growers Association 1972-73, 1972-1973 (Box 26)
- Northern Nut Growers Association hickory testing data 1969, 1969 (Box 26)
- Walnut testing 1969 - letters, 1969 (Box 26)
- Uncatalogued Northern Nut Growers Association material including correspondence, Date Unknown (Box 26)
- Wound dressing notes, Date Unknown (Box 26)
- Box of labeled slides, Date Unknown (Box 26)
- Correspondence, Date Unknown (Box 26)
- Correspondence - Gould Colman (2 folders), Date Unknown (Box 27)
- Marked copy of compost article, Date Unknown (Box 27)
- Report from Yugoslavia, Date Unknown (Box 27)
- Bulletin revision 1975 - Gortzig, 1975 (Box 27)
- Chestnut material, Date Unknown (Box 27)
- Correspondence, Date Unknown (Box 27)
- Coy Glen - 1978, 1978 (Box 27)
- Woodlot transfer, Date Unknown (Box 27)
- Horticulture-related correspondence, Date Unknown (Box 27)
- Manuscripts 1976-1977, 1976-1977 (Box 27)
- Northern Nut Growers Association 1976 - Chase, 1976 (Box 27)
  miscellaneous letters
- Plantations, Date Unknown (Box 27)
- Tree crop notes and manuscripts, Date Unknown (Box 27)
- Tree Crops Committee, Date Unknown (Box 27)
- Tree crops correspondence, Date Unknown (Box 27)
- Shade Tree Council 1977 - Dewitt Park, 1977 (Box 27)
- Correspondence answers not filed, Date Unknown (Box 27)
- Shade Tree Advisory Council A.B.C. DeWitt Park, Date Unknown (Box 27)
- Cayuga Lake Conservation Association, Date Unknown (Box 27)
- Paleontological Route 96 1977, 1977 (Box 27)
- Nuclear, 1977 (Box 27)
- Natural Areas Committee, Date Unknown (Box 27)
- Letters to editor - Route 96, Date Unknown (Box 27)
- Envelope - Jeanette B. McCay, Date Unknown (Box 27)
- Cayuga Lake Preservation Association working folder 1973, 1973 (Box 27)
- The Nature Conservancy, Date Unknown (Box 27)
- Government Cook - etc., Date Unknown (Box 27)
- Journal Clippings - 1973-74, 1973-1974 (Box 27)
- Environmental Management Council, Date Unknown (Box 27)
- Cayuga Lake Preservation Association - working draft - Cayuga Lake Basin Board, Date Unknown (Box 27)
- Correspondence and Cayuga Lake Preservation Association and Environmental Management Council-related, Date Unknown (Box 27)
- Environmental Management Council, 1970-10 (Box 27)
  miscellaneous letters October 1970
- Environmental Management Council 1972 minutes, 1972 (Box 27)
- Greenbelt - appendix material September 1972, 1972-09 (Box 27)
- Greenbelt - active manuscripts September 1972, 1972-09 (Box 27)
- Northern Nut Growers Association - 1971, 1971 (Box 27)
- Black Walnut Pruning 1975-76, 1975-1976 (Box 27)
- Northern Nut Growers Association - Black Walnut Testing - 1975-76, 1975-1976 (Box 27)
- Northern Nut Growers Association testing - score cards 1973-74 letters, 1973-1974 (Box 27)
- Fluoridation material, Date Unknown (Box 28)
- Miscellaneous and sorted material on fluoride, Date Unknown (Box 28)
- Walnut woodlot planting - walnut logs, Date Unknown (Box 28)
- Photo - Avery Skutt c. 1935, 1935 (Box 28)
- Nut related correspondence, Date Unknown (Box 28)
- Hickory germ plasm June 1974 Richard Jaynes, 1974-06 (Box 28)
- Conservationist - nut article manuscript, Date Unknown (Box 28)
- Manuscript - "Hazelnuts in New York State", Date Unknown (Box 28)
- Northern Nut Growers Association handbook, Date Unknown (Box 28)
- North American Lily Society - Judges 1972 meeting - Detroit, 1972 (Box 28)
- Lily correspondence, Date Unknown (Box 28)
- Northern Nut Growers Association correspondence, Date Unknown (Box 28)
- Letter from G. Slate 1969, 1969 (Box 28)
- Miscellaneous correspondence and material, Date Unknown (Box 28)
- Norther Nut Growers Association handbook judging - manuscripts, Date Unknown (Box 28)
- Correspondence, Date Unknown (Box 28)
- Nut growers yearbook 1966, 1966 (Box 28)
- Northern Nut Growers Association meeting - 1970 - preliminary arrangements and correspondence, 1970 (Box 28)
- Northern Nut Growers Association 1969 hickory papers, 1969 (Box 28)
- Northern Nut Growers Association - Michigan 1969 - general material, 1969 (Box 28)
- Woodroof manuscripts 1966, 1966 (Box 28)
- Northern Nut Growers Association handbook - general - Jaynes, Date Unknown (Box 28)
- Nut judging, Date Unknown (Box 28)
- Propogation, Date Unknown (Box 28)
- Northern Nut Growers Association - handbook manuscripts - propagation chapter, Date Unknown (Box 28)
- G. Slate Files, Date Unknown (Box 29)
- Nut extension letters - 1961, 1961 (Box 29)
- Northern nut growers program - 1961, 1961 (Box 29)
- Northern nut growers - 1961 program correspondence, 1961 (Box 29)
- Northern Nut Growers Association state college 1961, 1961 (Box 29)
- Mostly bulletins and memo material on nuts, Date Unknown (Box 29)
- Nut growers 1961 testing, 1961 (Box 29)
- Northern Nut Growers Association handbook revisions 1976-77 Jaynes, 1976-1977 (Box 29)
- Slate correspondence - 1977 yearbook, 1977 (Box 29)
- Slate - personal correspondence 1968-July 1, 1974, 1968-1974 (Box 29)
- Slate - lily material, Date Unknown (Box 29)
- Paztcuaro material, Date Unknown (Box 30)
  correspondence, field notes, photos, etc.
- Correspondence, Date Unknown (Box 30)
- Lily material and correspondence, Date Unknown (Box 30)
- Lily judging 1967, 1967 (Box 30)
- G. Slate correspondence, Date Unknown (Box 30)
- Lily judging 1965 - Urbana Show, 1965 (Box 30)
- Lily Society registration blanks, Date Unknown (Box 30)
- Correspondence - G. Slate, Date Unknown (Box 30)
- Tests for student judges - registration blanks, Date Unknown (Box 30)
- Lilies - miscellaneous letters 1965, 1965 (Box 30)
- Lily Society 1965 - show Urbana, 1965 (Box 30)
- Urbana Show - 2nd level exam, 1965 (Box 30)
- Lilies - miscellaneous correspondence 1965, 1965 (Box 30)
- Lilies - miscellaneous correspondence 1964, 1964 (Box 30)
- Lily judging 1966, 1966 (Box 30)
- Lily show 1963, 1963 (Box 30)
- Exam questions for student judges, Date Unknown (Box 30)
- Lily judging - Hamilton show 1964, 1964 (Box 30)
- Notes from the 10th annual International Botanical Congress, 1964 (Box 30)
- Manuscript: "Theory of the Derivations of the Diclinous Flowers of Carica papaya" - W.B. Storey, Date Unknown (Box 30)
- Northern Nut Growers Association correspondence, Date Unknown (Box 30)
- Notes and correspondence, Date Unknown (Box 30)
- DeWitt Park 1973, 1973 (Box 30)
- Florida Letters - 1972, 1972 (Box 30)
- Attention June 1972, 1972 (Box 30)
- Eames Bog, Date Unknown (Box 30)
- Tree crops, Date Unknown (Box 30)
- Tree crops - 1977, 1977 (Box 30)
- Tree crops - Bio Science - article, Date Unknown (Box 30)
- Tree crops - 1978, 1978 (Box 30)
- Tree crops - 1977 working folder article for science-cited reference, 1977 (Box 30)
- Tree crops - manuscript - June 1978 revision, 1978 (Box 30)
- Tree crops - extra copies - reports and references, Date Unknown (Box 30)
- Notes - New Caledonia 1949-50, 1949-1950 (Box 31)
- Notes - Philippines 1958, 1958 (Box 31)
- Miscellaneous materials, 1944-1945 (Box 31)
  notes from 1944-45 Lebanon and United Nations Relief and Rehabilitation Administration Albanian Mission
- Envelope, Notes Yugoslavia 1960-61 - photos, 1960-1961 (Box 31)
- Envelope, notes Yugoslavia 1961-62, 1961-19621 (Box 31)
- Maps, Yugoslavia, Date Unknown (Box 31)
- Correspondence 1961, 1961 (Box 31)
- Envelope, United Fruit Company - banana research 1961, 1961 (Box 31)
- Garden Book 1963, 1963 (Box 31)
- Temperature studies, records, Date Unknown (Box 31)
- Frost studies and (photos), Date Unknown (Box 31)
- Plant List for Garden Club exhibit May 1969, 1969-05 (Box 31)
- Journal clippings 1973 (mainly conservation), 1973 (Box 31)
- Draft - tentative plan Cayuga Lake Basin 1973, 1973 (Box 31)
- Walnut Bunch 1975, 1975 (Box 31)
- Bunch June-July 1975, 1975-06-1975-07 (Box 31)
- Walnut Bunch Disease - main folder, notes, Date Unknown (Box 31)
- Bunch photos 1981, 1981 (Box 31)
- Bunch Seliskar articles, Date Unknown (Box 31)
- Organic gardening manuscript 1975, 1975 (Box 31)
- Northern Nut Growers Association article on hickory shell structure photos, Date Unknown (Box 31)
- Photos - hickory, miscellaneous and general, Date Unknown (Box 31)
- Nut Bulletin 701 Prints - duplicated, extras, Date Unknown (Box 31)
- Nut bulletin revision Photos 1974, 1974 (Box 31)
- Northern Nut Growers Association convention material and other 1970 items, 1970 (Box 31)
- Nut Photos returned from Conservationist article, Date Unknown (Box 31)
- Master marked copy "Judging Nut Crops", Date Unknown (Box 31)
- 1968 questionnaires nut tree (Thomas) survey letters sent, 1968 (Box 31)
- 1968 questionnaires nut tree (Thomas) survey letters not sent, 1968 (Box 31)
- Various photos: George Slate's Garden, Date Unknown (Box 31)